University Photography Photograph Collection UA206
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 2005 -- 2006; UA206.001; 3347 Digital Object(s)
  - Job 051019 NSO Engineer Fair, 2005; UA206.001.301; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 228, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00036; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 182, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00037; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 141, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00038; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 131, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00039; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 115, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00040; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 180, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00041; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 139, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00042; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 071, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00043; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 064, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00044; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 050, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00045; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 317, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00046; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 304, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00047; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 210, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00048; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 194, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00049; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 155, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00050; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 109, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00051; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 090, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00052; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 069, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00053; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 044, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00054; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 024, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00055; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 038, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00056; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 027, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00057; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 122, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00058; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 100, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00059; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 081, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00060; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 059, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00061; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 037, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00062; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 259, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00063; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 227, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00064; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 206, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00065; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 160, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00066; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 120, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00067; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 105, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00068; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 091, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00069; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 076, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00070; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 056, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00071; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 323, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00072; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 314, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00073; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 295, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00074; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 256, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00075; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 222, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00076; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 198, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00077; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 145, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00078; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 097, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00079; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 085, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00080; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 143, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00081; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 135, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00082; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 004, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00083; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 075, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00084; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 066, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00085; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Engineering students present their projects in Cousens Gym. Photo 018, 2005-10-19; UA206.001.301.00086; Sobecki, Nicki
  - Job 051019 VLU Blaser, 2005; UA206.001.302; Lukasova, Veronika
  - Job 051020 JTO Field Hockey, 2005; UA206.001.303; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051021 JTO Conference, 2005; UA206.001.304; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051021 JTO Regatta, 2005; UA206.001.305; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 031, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00001; Tobin, Joanie
      Head of the Charles regatta.
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 006, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00002; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 014, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00003; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 015, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00004; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 085, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00005; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 025, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00006; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 037, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00007; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 018, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00008; Tobin, Joanie
    - Head of the Charles regatta. Photo 036, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.305.00009; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051021 MKO Blix, 2005; UA206.001.306; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051021 SAR Arab Night, 2005; UA206.001.307; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 024, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00001; Arkin, Sarah
      Arab Night on the residential quad.
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 032, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00002; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 005, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00003; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 038, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00004; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 020, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00005; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 025, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00006; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 007, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00007; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 009, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00008; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 017, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00009; Arkin, Sarah
    - Arab Night on the residential quad. Photo 021, 2005-10-21; UA206.001.307.00010; Arkin, Sarah
  - Job 051022 MKO Crew, 2005; UA206.001.308; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 107, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00001; Ko, Melody
      Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor.
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 056, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00002; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 038, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00003; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 012, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00004; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 102, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00005; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 043, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00006; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 025, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00007; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 036, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00008; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 007, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00009; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 027, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00010; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 080, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00011; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 013, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00012; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 054, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00013; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 060, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00014; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 037, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00015; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 108, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00016; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 052, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00017; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 035, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00018; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 091, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00019; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 048, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00020; Ko, Melody
    - Crew team's 13th annual Boat Cruise on the harbor. Photo 069, 2005-10-22; UA206.001.308.00021; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051023 JTO Child Development, 2005; UA206.001.309; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051024 ASC construction, 2005; UA206.001.310; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Construction update for the new music building and Sophia Gordon Hall. Photo 004, 2005-10-24; UA206.001.310.00001; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Construction update for the new music building and Sophia Gordon Hall. Photo 001, 2005-10-24; UA206.001.310.00002; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Construction update for the new music building and Sophia Gordon Hall. Photo 003, 2005-10-24; UA206.001.310.00003; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Construction update for the new music building and Sophia Gordon Hall. Photo 005, 2005-10-24; UA206.001.310.00004; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Construction update for the new music building and Sophia Gordon Hall. Photo 002, 2005-10-24; UA206.001.310.00005; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 051024 MKO Griffiths, 2005; UA206.001.311; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051024 MKO Labs, 2005; UA206.001.312; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051024 MKO Sackler, 2005; UA206.001.313; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051024 MKO Sonnenschein, 2005; UA206.001.314; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051024 MKO Soto, 2005; UA206.001.315; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051024 SAR United Nations Day, 2005; UA206.001.316; Arkin, Sarah
  - Job 051025 MKO Rally, 2005; UA206.001.317; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051025 MMO Friedman Fellows, 2005; UA206.001.318; Morelli, Mark
  - Job 051025 ZTZ Borgers, 2005; UA206.001.319; Tzanev, Zara
    - Mathematics professor Christophe Borgers. Photo 005, 2005-10-25; UA206.001.319.00001; Tzanev, Zara
      Mathematics professor Christophe Borgers.
  - Job 051026 BWE campus, 2005; UA206.001.320; Weller, Bruce
  - Job 051026 MKO Grafton, 2005; UA206.001.321; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051026 VLU Elnekave, 2005; UA206.001.322; Lukasova, Veronika
  - Job 051028 JTO Sailing, 2005; UA206.001.323; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051028 MMO Red Cross, 2005; UA206.001.324; Morelli, Mark
  - Job 051030 JTO Bend, 2005; UA206.001.325; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051030 JTO Sackler, 2005; UA206.001.326; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051030 NSO campus, 2005; UA206.001.327; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 030, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00001; Sobecki, Nicki
      Canon images.
    - Canon images. Photo 012, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00002; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 024, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00003; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 019, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00004; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 031, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00005; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 005, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00006; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 027, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00007; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 025, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00008; Sobecki, Nicki
    - Canon images. Photo 002, 2005-10-30; UA206.001.327.00009; Sobecki, Nicki
  - Job 051031 ASC campus, 2005; UA206.001.328; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 051031 ASC construction, 2005; UA206.001.329; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 051031 JTO Foliage, 2005; UA206.001.330; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 001, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00001; Tobin, Joanie
      Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn.
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 004, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00002; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 006, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00003; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 014, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00004; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 019, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00005; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 025, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00006; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 026, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00007; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 033, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00008; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 041, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00009; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 047, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00010; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 056, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00011; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 064, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00012; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 069, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00013; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 075, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00014; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 085, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00015; Tobin, Joanie
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including fall foliage shots of the President's Lawn. Photo 087, 2005-10-31; UA206.001.330.00016; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051031 MKO Anwar, 2005; UA206.001.331; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051031 MKO Smith Freeman, 2005; UA206.001.332; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051031 MKO Thankey Anwer, 2005; UA206.001.333; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051101 NSO Cannon, 2005; UA206.001.334; Sobecki, Nicki
  - Job 051101 SAR campus, 2005; UA206.001.335; Arkin, Sarah
  - Job 051102 JTO Mens Soccer, 2005; UA206.001.336; Tobin, Joanie
  - Job 051102 MKO Break Dance, 2005; UA206.001.337; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 025, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00001; Ko, Melody
      B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Alien Ness, who is also known as Luis Martinez, is legendary among b-boys and has performed with many breakdancing crews, including the New York City Breakers and the Rock Steady Crew.
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 027, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00002; Ko, Melody
      B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Alien Ness, who is also known as Luis Martinez, is legendary among b-boys and has performed with many crews including the New York City Breakers and the Rock Steady Crew.
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 035, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00003; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 048, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00004; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 055, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00005; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 057, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00006; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 067, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00007; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 068, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00008; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 071, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00009; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 074, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00010; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 079, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00011; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 085, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00012; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 089, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00013; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 096, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00014; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 102, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00015; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 105, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00016; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 108, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00017; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 116, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00018; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 117, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00019; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 124, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00020; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 139, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00021; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 156, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00022; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 157, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00023; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 163, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00024; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 164, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00025; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 165, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00026; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 178, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00027; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 206, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00028; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 211, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00029; Ko, Melody
    - B-Boy Alien Ness visited campus to teach students the art of "breaking" at the Jackson Gym Monday. Photo 223, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.337.00030; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051102 MKO Lofgren Hoffman, 2005; UA206.001.338; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051102 MKO Vet Stock, 2005; UA206.001.339; Ko, Melody
  - Job 051102 SAR campus, 2005; UA206.001.340; Arkin, Sarah
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus in autumn, including the president's lawn. Photo 014, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.340.00001; Arkin, Sarah
      Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus in autumn, including the president's lawn.
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus in autumn, including the president's lawn. Photo 015, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.340.00002; Arkin, Sarah
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus in autumn, including the president's lawn. Photo 013, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.340.00003; Arkin, Sarah
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus in autumn, including the president's lawn. Photo 019, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.340.00004; Arkin, Sarah
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus in autumn, including the president's lawn. Photo 012, 2005-11-02; UA206.001.340.00005; Arkin, Sarah